<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>stoicism on Lightbi</title>
    <link>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/tags/stoicism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in stoicism on Lightbi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>sample@gmail.com (Bino Kochumol Varghese)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>sample@gmail.com (Bino Kochumol Varghese)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/tags/stoicism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Who am I ?!</title>
      <link>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/who-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>sample@gmail.com (Bino Kochumol Varghese)</author>
      <guid>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/who-am-i/</guid>
      <description>Who am I ?! This is the most asked question in my life. Yet no clear answer has yet been found.
As a child, the answer to this question was simple. Say my name to the question of who. Aha ..! Simple and beautiful. In that answer, parents and siblings in adolescence. I thought to myself that the answer was too clear.
When I started asking myself this question at a young age when I was beginning to recognize many things, I began to feel that the answer was becoming less clear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown</title>
      <link>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/stoicism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>sample@gmail.com (Bino Kochumol Varghese)</author>
      <guid>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/stoicism/</guid>
      <description>What is Markdown?
The Markdown Guide is a free and open-source reference guide that explains how to use Markdown, the simple and easy-to-use markup language you can use to format virtually any document.
Markdown is a lightweight markup language that you can use to add formatting elements to plaintext text documents. Created by John Gruber in 2004, Markdown is now one of the world’s most popular markup languages.
Using Markdown is different than using a WYSIWYG editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stoic Philosophers?</title>
      <link>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/stoicism3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>sample@gmail.com (Bino Kochumol Varghese)</author>
      <guid>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/stoicism3/</guid>
      <description>Agasicles, king of the Spartans, once quipped that he wanted to be “the student of men whose son I should like to be as well.” It is a critical consideration we need to make in our search for role models. Stoicism is no exception. Before we begin our studies we need to ask ourselves: Who are the people that followed these precepts? Who can I point out as an example? Am I proud to look up to this person?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Did Stoicism Begin?</title>
      <link>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/stoicism2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>sample@gmail.com (Bino Kochumol Varghese)</author>
      <guid>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/stoicism2/</guid>
      <description>Around 304 BC, a merchant named Zeno was shipwrecked on a trading voyage. He lost nearly everything. Making his way to Athens, he was introduced to philosophy by the Cynic philosopher Crates and the Megarian philosopher Stilpo, which changed his life. As Zeno later joked, “I made a prosperous voyage when I suffered shipwreck.” He would later move to what became known as the Stoa Poikile, literally meaning “painted porch.” Erected in the 5th century BC—the ruins of it are visible still, some 2,500 years later—the painted porch is where Zeno and his disciples gathered for discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Stoicism?</title>
      <link>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/stoicism1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>sample@gmail.com (Bino Kochumol Varghese)</author>
      <guid>https://lightbi-hugo-theme.netlify.app/post/2020/jan/stoicism1/</guid>
      <description>The private diaries of one of Rome’s greatest emperors, the personal letters of one of Rome’s best playwrights and wisest power brokers, the lectures of a former slave and exile, turned influential teacher. Against all odds, some two millennia later, these incredible documents survive. They contain some of the greatest wisdom in the history of the world and together, they constitute the bedrock of what is known as Stoicism—an ancient philosophy that was once one of the most popular civic disciplines in the West, practiced by the rich and the impoverished, the powerful and the struggling alike in the pursuit of the Good Life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>